Worried about losing your settings due to Quanto Flx updates or other mishaps? Back them up! You can back up the settings of each package, or use the Backup Wizard to back up all settings.
A package may contain multiple pages. When the interface does not accommodate these tabs, place the cursor on the tab bar and use the mouse wheel to browse them.
Configure your system monitoring software, and you will get a richer system monitoring feature provided by Quanto Flx System.
When a scroll bar appears where the cursor is, it means you can scroll the mouse wheel to browse the content.
When using a text box, press Enter to apply changes, or press Esc or click other area to cancel typing.
You can find more detailed solutions in the Quanto Flx Wiki. Click the "Help" button above to go to.
Not satisfied with the preset appearance provided? You can adjust them through the Global Settings.
Use the "Combine" function in the skin settings to make your layout neater and less fragmented.
To actively explore more features of the skin, press the right button to start.
You can use the "Rulers" in Quanto Flx Miscellaneous to align your layout.
If you find your device running slow, try unloading some skins.
Middle-click a skin to toggle its style/size (if available).
Found a problem? Please report it via Github or email.
To batch drag, hold Ctrl+Alt to select skins and drag.
Please make sure that your Rainmeter is up to date.
If the skin shows abnormality, try to refresh it.
We never gonna give you up!